i gotta say something real quick i get a lot of flack from folks men women the like talking about
oh she's so opinionated she's too much she's still opinionated no i'm not opinionated i'm informed
see that's the difference between me and y'all who say shit like that you talk out your neck
everywhere on this internet because you have nothing really of value to say about things
that actually have impact and you can hide behind the anonymity of this shit i'm out here
i'm out here i'm in yo city i'm in nay city i'm on this internet i am accessible and i'm saying
things that actually have merit and value because they are fact-checked and they are supported by
actual shit so no we not the same me and you them folks who be saying that to me you talking about
gossip you talking about nonsense you talking about people you don't even know i do this for a living
you do this to feel alive
you